

    * [Unity LevelPlay
        
        Mediation](https://www.is.com/mediation/)
    * [ironSource Network
        
        Ad network](https://www.is.com/user-growth/#inappadvertising)
    * [Tapjoy
        
        Offerwall](https://www.is.com/tapjoy/)
    * [Aura
        
        On-device solutions](https://www.is.com/aura/)
    * [Supersonic
        
        Publishing](https://supersonic.com/)
    * [Luna
        
        Cross-channel management](https://luna.is.com/)

    * [Ad mediation
        
        Unity LevelPlay](https://www.is.com/mediation/)
    * [In-app ad network
        
        ironSource Ads](https://www.is.com/monetization/#network)
    * [Offerwall
        
        Tapjoy](https://www.is.com/tapjoy/)
    * [On-device solutions
        
        Aura](https://www.is.com/aura/)
    * [ironSource Exchange
        
        ironSource Exchange](https://www.is.com/ironsource-exchange/)
    * [Publishing
        
        Supersonic](https://supersonic.com/)

            Implementing ads without cannibalizing subscription conversions: A brief guide by ad format

#### ironSource Website Privacy Policy

Last Updated: August 6th, 2024

The following policy governs how ironSource Ltd. (“ironSource“, “Company” “we” or “us“), and its subsidiaries, handle information collected from users of its websites, at the addresses [is.com/](https://www.is.com/), lunalabs.io/, bidalgo.com/, tapjoy.com/ and their subdomains (the “Sites“), including ironSource Mobile Dashboard, Tapjoy Dashboard, Luna Create Hub and the Luna Control Hub (the “Dashboards”).

Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Use available on the Site, which this Privacy Policy is incorporated thereto by reference.

Please note that this privacy policy covers our privacy practices only with respect to the Sites.

If you would like to review our privacy policies for our products and services, please see the links below:

Mobile Ad Network and Mediation Platform – [https://developers.ironsrc.com/ironsource-mobile/air/ironsource-mobile-privacy-policy/](https://developers.ironsrc.com/ironsource-mobile/air/ironsource-mobile-privacy-policy/)

Supersonic Studios Apps – [https://supersonic.com/privacy/](https://supersonic.com/privacy/)

Tapjoy’s privacy policy – [https://dev.tapjoy.com/en/legal/Privacy-Policy](https://dev.tapjoy.com/en/legal/Privacy-Policy)

The Sites are accessible for individuals around the world. Accordingly, throughout the document, we try to harmonize our approach and the language of the privacy policy as much as possible. However, sometimes we refer to specific laws that require further disclosures. These disclosures cover laws and regulations applicable to the following regions:

1. Individuals who we deem to be located in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, or Switzerland – With respect to the collection and processing of their personal data, as defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), and the UK Data Protection Act.
2. If you are a resident of California, Virginia, Connecticut, Colorado, Utah, Florida, Oregon, Texas, Montana, Delaware, Iowa, Nebraska, New Hampshire and New Jersey – please see “State Privacy Rights” section of this privacy policy for information related to privacy laws in these states.

Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!) BY ACCESSING THE SITES AND/OR USING THE SITES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THE “PRIVACY POLICY“), INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITES.

Information We Collect, and Purposes of Processing

We collect the following types of information from Users:

1. Information collected automatically from Users who are visiting the Sites (“Site Information”):

* Technical Information – Technical information about your browser and device is automatically collected when you visit the Sites, or the Dashboard apps. Such information consists of the device’s IP address, device ID, the type and version of browser used to access the Sites, operating system, language of the browser and operating system, and type of device.
* Interaction Information – Information about your interactions with the Sites or Dashboard apps (e.g. whether you clicked on a specific link, where you clicked, time on Sites, etc.).

3. Information you voluntarily provide us:

* Registration Information – When you register to our services, you will be asked to provide your email address, password, billing information, details about your apps, and payment details.
* Job Application Information – When you choose to apply for a job at ironSource via the Sites, you will be requested to provide us with your full name, email address, phone number, link to your Linkedin page, link to your website, and your CV.
* Newsletter Information – If you subscribe to our newsletter, you will be requested to provide your email address.
* Event Information – If you choose to register to an event we host, you will be requested to provide us with your full name, email address, phone number, job title, current company, and such other information necessary for attending the event.
* Communication Information – If you choose to communicate with us via an online form on the Sites, email, or automated chat service (‘chat bot’), you may provide us with information such as your name, and your email address, and any other information you choose to share with us.
* Luna Create Hub Service Information – If you use Luna Create Hub, you may permit us to upload your video creatives to your YouTube channel on your behalf, using YouTube API Services, by logging in to your YouTube account and providing us with your account’s session token. By using Luna Create Hub in that manner, you agree to be bound by the YouTube terms of service, available [here](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms). You may revoke our access to that information at any time via the Google security settings page [here](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions). You can find more information about Google’s privacy practices in the Google Privacy Policy, available [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy).

What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?

1. We use the information we collect for the following purposes:

Sharing Information with Third Parties

We may share information with our subsidiaries and affiliated companies, and with vendors and service providers for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may also disclose information if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our agreements and policies, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) investigate, detect, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud or security issues; (iv) to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims; (v) prevent harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users, yourself or any third party; (vi) for the purpose of collaborating with law enforcement agencies or in case we find it necessary in order to enforce intellectual property or other legal rights; or (vii) when we are undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of our assets.

Deletion or Modification of Personal Information

If for any reason you wish to modify or delete your Personal Information please send us an email to website-privacy-request@ironsrc.com, and we will make reasonable efforts to modify or delete any such Personal Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws.

Retention of Information

We store information for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected, as explained in this privacy policy. In some circumstances we may store information for longer periods of time, for instance where we are required to do so in accordance with legal, regulatory, tax, accounting requirements.

Minors

To use the Sites, you must be over the age of eighteen (18). Therefore, ironSource does not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18) and does not wish to do so. If you have any reason to believe that a minor has shared Personal Information with us, please contact us.

Third Party Sites

While using the Sites you may encounter links to third party websites. Please be advised that such third party websites are independent sites, and we assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such websites.

Cookies

When you access or use the Sites, we may use industry-wide technologies such as “cookies” (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your service experience much more convenient and effortless. It is easy to prohibit certain cookies. You can do so by editing your preferences through the Site’s cookie settings link. In addition, most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited.

Information to Individuals Located in the European Economic Area, Switzerland, and the United Kingdom

1. International Transfers – We store personal data on our Amazon Web Services servers in the United States, and on the servers of our processors, which may be located outside of the European Union, or the United Kingdom. We will transfer personal data countries which are recognized as providing an adequate level of legal protection or where we can be satisfied that alternative arrangement are in place to protect your privacy rights.
2. Your Rights – Data subjects have the right to request us to access, rectify or erase personal data that we process, or to restrict or object to its processing in accordance with the provisions of the GDPR. A data subject can submit a request for exercising these rights by sending us an email to website-privacy-request@ironsrc.com. Please note that we will process the request subject to verification of the consumer’s identity.

A data subject that chooses to withdraw consent can do that by the cookie settings available on the Site.

A data subject also has the right to file a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority (e.g. of the consumer’s country or domicile) where we have not addressed the data subject’s concerns.

State Privacy Rights

1. California, Virginia, Connecticut, Colorado, Utah, Florida, Oregon, Texas, Montana, Delaware, Iowa, Nebraska, New Hampshire and New Jersey residents have certain rights under state privacy laws with respect to personal data we collect. If you are a resident of such states, this section of the privacy policy contains disclosures required by law and explains rights that may be available to you.
2. In the past 12 months, we have collected, sold (including sharing for targeted advertising), and disclosed for business purposes the following categories of personal data. We do not knowingly sell, nor do we share or process for targeted advertising purposes, personal data about consumers under the age of 16.
 5. Our Purposes for Processing Personal Data – We use and disclose the personal data we collect for our commercial and business purposes, as further described above in the “Information We Collect, and Purposes of Processing” and the “Sharing Information With Third Parties” Sections.
6. Recipients of Personal Data Although we do not sell personal data for monetary consideration, we do sell personal data, including sharing for targeted advertising purposes, subject to the choices you make on the Site, to the categories of third parties listed below:

– Advertising Companies; and

– Analytics Providers.

9. Your Rights Regarding Personal Data – Residents of certain states have rights with respect to the personal data collected by businesses like ironSource. You may be able to exercise the following rights regarding your personal data, subject to certain exceptions and limitations:

* The right to confirm whether we are processing personal data about you.
* The right to correct inaccuracies in the personal data we have collected about you.
* The right to know the categories and specific pieces of personal data we collect, use, disclose, and sell about you, the categories of sources from which we collected your personal data, our purposes for collecting or selling your personal data, the categories of your personal data that we have either sold (including shared for targeted advertising purposes) or disclosed for a business purpose, and the categories of third parties with which we have disclosed personal data.
* The right to request that we delete the personal data we have collected or maintain about the you.
* The right to opt out of our sale of your personal data and our processing (including sharing) for targeted advertising purposes. Please note that if you opt out of certain practices, we may be unable to provide you with some services.
* The right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of the above privacy rights.

While some states provide residents with rights related to “sensitive” personal data, ironSource does not collect this type of personal data.

Exercise Your Rights

You can submit a request by sending us an email to website-privacy-request@ironsrc.com.

In order to exercise the right to opt out of our sale or sharing of your personal data, including for targeted advertising purposes, use the cookie settings provided in the Site.

Depending on your state, if you have submitted a request that we have not fulfilled, you may contact us to appeal our decision by sending an email with the subject line “Appeal” to website-privacy-request@ironsrc.com.

You may also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf by verifying your identity and providing the agent with a written permission to make the request on your behalf.

Verification Process and Required Information

Note that we may need to request additional information from you to verify your identity or process your request. You will not be required to create an account with us to submit a request or have it fulfilled. We will require you to provide, at a minimum, your email address and state of residence. We may also ask you to provide us a few of your device identifiers, so that we can verify your identity. Once we verify your identity, we will request additional information necessary to authenticate the request.

Information about California resident requests: As required by California law, ironSource has provided the following information about requests it received from California residents from June 1, 2023 to May 31, 2024.

Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may revise this privacy policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our processing of information and is posted at https://www.is.com/privacy-policy/. If we make a change to this policy, we will post the revised privacy policy to this page.

Contact Us:

ironSource Ltd., located at 121 Menachem Begin Rd., Tel Aviv, Israel, is the organization responsible for collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at ironsource\_privacy@unity3d.com.

Because email communications are not always secure, please do not include credit card or other sensitive information in your emails to us.

121 Menachem Begin Rd., Tel Aviv, Israel

Attn: Data Protection Officer

You can also contact us as follows:

* DPO@unity3d.com
* ironSource Ltd., 121 Menachem Begin Rd., Tel Aviv, Israel (Israel contact)
* Unity Technologies, 30 3rd Street, San Francisco, CA 94103 (United States contact)
* Unity Technologies ApS, Niels Hemmingsens Gade 24, 1153 Copenhagen, Denmark (European Union contact)
* Unity Technologies, GINZA SIX 8F, 6-10-1 Ginza, Chuo-ku, Tokyo Japan 104-0061 (Japan Contact)

For app developers

For mobile operators

Community

Company

2024 ironSource
